Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 486. A sermon about the Prophet's attributes and virtues, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 486)
  Side A: A recording of a sermon about some of the Prophet's attributes and virtues in which a speaker talks about honesty and satisfaction. The speaker presents the Prophet as an example for honesty and satisfaction and explains that they are of the most important attributes of the Prophet. The speaker tells pertinent stories from the Prophet's biography.
  Side B: A recording of another sermon in which a speaker tells a story about repentance. The speaker believes that the Islamic nation is in inattentiveness and criticizes the Muslim countries for not supporting Mujahideen in Afghanistan.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:57 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:57 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ???? ? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ? ???????. ???? ??????? ????? ?? ????? ???????? ??????? ???? ????? ??? ???? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ? ???? ????? ?? ??? ?? ?????? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ?? ???? ???? ???? ???? ??????? ??? ?? ??????. ????? ??????? ??? ????? ????????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ??? ?????? ????? ????????? ????????? ?? ?????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 487. Sermons about leaders and prayer, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 487)
  Comments: Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Audio quality is poor with background noise but is intelligible. Side A 44:16 min. Side B 44:29 min.
  Side A: A speaker tells stories in which he compares between Arabic rulers Caliphs such as Hafiz Al-Asad and ?Umar ibn al-Khat?t?a?b.
  Side B: A recording of a supplication and a sermon about prayer and how to approach to God. The speaker tells a supplication which the Prophet used to recite in his prayer during prostrating.
  ?????????: ?????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 44:16 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:29 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ????? ????? ???? ??? ???? ??? ???? ??????? ???????? ????? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ???? ?? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ??? ????. ???? ??????? ????? ??? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ??? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 488. A sermon on prayer and worship, Circa 1980-2000; 1 (Box 488)
  Comments: Side A 4:03 min. Side B 43:14 min.
  Side A: A speaker recites a supplication then directs his speech to the Muslim youth and tells stories about the role of ?Ali? ibn Abi? T?a?lib when he was young in defending Islam. The speaker talks about the result and penalty of abandoning any of the five daily prayers.
  Side B: The speaker discusses a statement of the former US president Ronald Regan about a potential war in the Middle East and talks and tells stories from the history of Islam about the principles of the Islamic religion.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 44:03 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:14 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ????? ? ???? ??????? ????? ? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ????? ??? ????? ?? ??? ?? ??? ???? ????? ??? ????? ? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ????? ????????. ????? ??????? ?? ??????? ????? ?????? ? ????? ??? ?? ????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ??????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ?????? ? ????? ?? ????? ????? ???????? ????? ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?? ???
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 490. A sermon on monotheism, Circa 1980-2000; 1 (Box 490)
  Comments: Side A 46:03 min. Side B 43:26 min.
  Side A: A speaker cites the advisory opinion of al-Sha?fi?i? on the oneness of God, recites supplications, and asks the audience to believe in the oneness of God.
  Side B: The speaker talks about massacre perpetrated by the regime of Hafiz Al-Asad in Syria and the people who killed because of the war between Iraq and Iran. The speaker criticizes extravagance and calls for social solidarity among Muslims.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:03 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:26 ?????
  ????? ?????: ?????? ??????? ???? ??????? ?? ??????? ???? ? ???? ??????? ????? ??? ??????. ???? ??????? ?????? ??? ??????? ???????? ????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?? ??? ???? ???? ????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ???????? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ? ?????. ????? ??????? ??????? ???????? ????? ??? ??????? ????????? ??? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 491. A sermon on Jihad in Palestine and Afghanistan, 1988; 1 (Box 491)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 46:43 min. Side B 46:34 min. Speaker: Usa?mah ibn La?din and others. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  0:00 to 23:14 The speaker gives a sermon on Jihad. He speaks about Jihad in Afghanistan and Palestine. He believes that warfare is the way to regain Jerusalem. He speaks about Mujahideen who fight the Russians in Afghanistan and mentions that the West was pleased with this fight. He mentions reports from the US National Security Council about Mujahideen and the possibility of establishing an Islamic state in Afghanistan. He also mentions that Mujahideen refused a request for a meeting from a delegate of the US State Department. He urges people to prepare for Jihad and get ready to fight and wage economic war on the West by boycotting American goods. He commends the decision of the "Martyr King"- without mentioning his name -- who cut off the oil supplies to USA and the West in 1973. He urges people to make a contribution to the Mujahideen through a committee of Prince Salma?n in Peshawar, Pakistan.
  23:20 to 28:10 The same speaker answers questions from the audience about the United States' attitude toward the Mujahideen and how to go to Afghanistan for Jihad. He also mentions the advisory opinion of some scholars, including al-Alba?ni? regarding having the consent of parents before going to Jihad, as well as Jihad fundraising committees in Saudi Arabia which are overseen by the deputy prince of Makkah, Sa?u?d ibn ?Abd al-Muh?sin.
  28:14 to 45:43 Another speaker gives a sermon in which he talks about the 40th anniversary of establishing the state of Israel, Jihad in Palestine, and the fight against Israelis. He speaks about the Vatican's position on the events in Palestine. He advises Palestinians to fight and disregard any peace conference or initiative. He speaks about "the transfer plan" which is prepared by Israel to deport the Palestinians beyond the Jordan River. He praises the Palestinians' resistance. He speaks about the Druze cooperation with Israel against Palestinians in Bala?t?ah refugee camp.
  45:44 to the end of side A, background noise.
  Side B: The same speaker on side A gives a sermon on Jihad. He speaks about the successive invasions of Palestine and al-Aqs?a? mosque from the time of ?Umar ibn al-Khat?t?a?b to S?ala?h? al-Di?n al-Ayyu?bi?, the Tatar invasion of the Islamic countries and Baghdad, and the fall of Andalusia. He emphasizes the importance of Jihad and cites Hadith on fighting the infidels. He tells in detail stories about battles fought by him with the Mujahideen in Afghanistan and mentions some names of those who were killed in those battles. He recalls the obligation of Jihad and cites the opinion of ibn Taymi?yah on this topic. He mentions the availability of discounted flight tickets to Islamabad then to Peshawar in Pakistan and then to Afghanistan to join Mujahideen. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:43 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:34 ?????. ???????: ????? ?? ???? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 23:14 ??????? ???? ???? ?? ??????. ????? ?? ?????? ?? ?????? ??????????. ??? ?? ?????? ?? ?????? ???????? ????? ???? ????? ????????. ????? ?? ???? ????????? ????? ?? ????????? ????? ??? ????? ????? ??????? ????? ????????? ????? ?? ????????? ?????? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ?????? ???????? ??? ????????? ?? ????????? ???????? ??????? ????? ??????? ????. ???? ??? ????? ????? ???????? ????????? ??????? ????????? ?? ????????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ???? ???. ??? ????? ??? ????????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ??? ?????? ??? ????? ?????????? ??? ????? ??????? ??????? ????????? ????? ????? "????? ??????- ??? ??? ????" ???? ??????? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??? 1973. ??? ??? ??? ???????? ??? ????????? ?? ???? ???? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ???????
  ?? 23:20 ??? 28:10 ??? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ???? ?????? ?? ?????????, ????? ?????? ??? ????????? ??????, ????? ???? ????? ??? ????? ???????? ?? ??? ?????? ???????? ??? ?????? ??? ??????, ???? ??? ???????? ????????? ?? ???????? ????? ???? ????? ???? ???? ??? ???? ??? ??? ??????
  ?? 28:14 ??? 45:43 ????? ??? ???? ???? ?? ???? 40 ??? ??? ????? ???? ??????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ????????????. ????? ?? ????????? ??????? ??? ???? ?? ??????. ???? ??????????? ??????? ???? ???????? ??????? ?? ??????? ??????. ????? ?? ??? ???? "??????????"??? ??? ??????? ?????? ??????????? ??? ?? ???? ??? ??????. ???? ??????? ??????????? ???????? ????????. ????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ??????????? ?? ???? ?????
  ?? 45:44 ??? ????? ????? ????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ??????? ????? ?? ????? ????? ???? ???? ?? ??????. ????? ?? ??????? ????????? ??? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ??? ??? ?? ?????? ?????? ????? ????? ???????, ??? ?????? ?????? ????????? ??????? ??? ?????, ????? ??????? ?? ???? ????????. ???? ??? ????? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? ??? ????? ?????? ?? ??????. ???? ???????? ??? ?? ????? ????? ?? ????????? ?? ????????? ????? ????? ??? ???? ??? ??? ?? ??? ???????. ???? ?????? ????? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ???. ???? ???? ????? ????? ????? ??? ????? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ??????? ??? ?? ??? ????????? ???????? ??????????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 492. A recitation from the Qur?a?n and sermon, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 492)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 46:32 min. Side B 43:57 min. Speaker: Muh?ammad S?iddi?q al-Minsha?wi? and others. Place: Unknown.
  0:00 to 28:55 The tape starts with an introduction to the recording by Al-ra?yah Islamic Recordings followed by a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura A?l ?Umra?n verses 92 – 155.
  28:56 to 43:27 Background noise.
  43:28 to the end of side A, A speaker gives a sermon on Druze cooperation with Israel against Palestinians in Bala?t?ah refugee camp (the same recording on Cassette #491, Side A). The recording cuts off at the end of side A.
  0:00 to 28:22 A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat A?l ?Umra?n verses 156-200 and al-Nisa?? verses 1-18.
  28:23 to the end of side B, A speaker gives a sermon on Jihad. He emphasizes the importance of Jihad and cites Hadith on fighting the infidels (the same recording on Cassette #491, Side B). The recording is interrupted by a call for prayer, and then the same sermon continues and the recording cuts of at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:32 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:57?????. ???????: ???? ???? ???????? ??????. ??????: ??? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 28:55 ???? ?????? ?????? ????? ??????? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ????????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ????? 92 ??? 155
  ?? 28:56 ??? 43:27 ?????
  ?? 43:28 ??? ????? ????? ????? ????? ???? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ??????????? ?? ???? ????? ( ??? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?? ???? ?? 491). ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 28:22 ????? ?? ?????? ???? ?? ????? ????? 156 ??? 200 ??????? ????? 1 ??? 18
  ?? 28:23 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ???? ???? ?? ??????. ???? ??? ????? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? ??? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ( ??? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ???? ?? 491). ???? ??????? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 493. A sermon on Jihad, Circa 1987-2000; 1 (Box 493)
  Comments: There are two recordings on the tape on side A from 0:00 to 1:42.Side A 31:33 min. Side B 31:53 min. Speaker: One of the speakers is most likely Usa?mah ibn La?din. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  0:00 to 1:42 The tape starts with a speaker who talks about understanding the Qur?a?n, commiting to it and acting according to it.
  1:43 to 14:09 A different speaker gives a sermon in which he describes in detail battles fought by him and the Mujahideen, mentioning their names and where they are from. He urges Jihad in Palestine.
  14:10 to the end of side A, another sermon by the same second speaker about preparing to fight the infidels. He cites the advisory opinion of Muh?ammad ibn ?Uthaymi?n, and he speaks about opening training camps for Mujahideen in Saudi Arabia. He answers questions from the audience about preparing for Jihad and Jihad in Palestine.
  0:00 to 20:54 continuation of the last sermon on side A. The speaker answers questions from the audience about how to get parents to consent to their children going for Jihad, the role of Muslim women in Jihad, the role of physicians and engineers in Jihad, providing aid and weapons to Mujahideen, and the latest news of Mujahideen in Afghanistan. He mentions the names of specific Mujahideen who have been injured in battles.
  21:07 to the end of side B, Another speaker starts a sermon by welcoming the audience at a Mujahideen base in Afghanistan. He speaks about the status of the Islamic nation and also the problems experienced by it. He urges the audience to follow the promotion of virtue and the prevention of vice. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ???? ??????? ?? ??? ???? ?? ????? ????? ?? 0:00 ??? 1:42. ??? ????? ????? 31:33 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:53 ?????. ???????: ??? ????????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ????. ??????: ????????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 1:42 ???? ?????? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ?????? ????????? ?????? ??
  ?? 1:43 ??? 14:09 ????? ??? ???? ???? ??? ???? ???????? ????? ????? ?? ????????? ????? ??????? ???????? ???? ???? ????. ??? ??? ?????? ?? ??????
  ?? 14:10 ??? ????? ????? ????? ???? ???? ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ???? ??????? ????? ?????? ??????? ???? ???? ?? ??????. ????? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ????????? ?? ????????. ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?????? ??????? ?? ??????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 20:54 ????? ???? ???? ?? ????? ?????. ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????, ??? ?????? ??????? ?? ??????, ??? ??????? ?????????? ?? ??????, ????? ????????? ??????? ?????????, ???? ????? ????????? ?? ?????????. ?????? ?? ??? ??????? ???? ???? ?? ??? ??????? ???? ?? ????????? ?? ??? ???????
  ?? 21:07 ??? ????? ????? ??????, ????? ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ??????? ?? ??? ????????? ?? ?????????. ????? ?? ??? ????? ????????? ???????? ???? ???????. ???? ????? ????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ?? ??????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 494. Jihad in Palestine and Afghanistan, Circa 1988-2000; 1 (Box 494)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 31:23 min. Side B 31:02 min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Usa?mah ibn La?din. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker gives a lecture in which he talks about supporting the Palestinians in their fight against Israel, the influx of Russian Jewish people to Israel, and the American grant to Israel to settle the new immigrants. He mentions James Baker's statement on the unconditioned US support of the Jewish immigration. He calls for a fight against Israel. He relates some historical events about the infidels' treatment of the Prophet's companions. He urges people to prepare for Jihad and get ready to fight and wage economic war on the United States. He speaks about the US support for John Garang in Sudan. The recording cuts off at the end of side A.
  0:00 to 27:22 Continuation of the same lecture on side A. The speaker talks about Jihad and urges people to go to Afghanistan. He answers questions from the audience about the role of youth in Jihad, Jihad in Palestine and Afghanistan, and getting consent from parents to go for Jihad. He reviews the advisory opinion of various scholars in Jihad and cites the opinion of al-Alba?ni? and ibn Taymi?yah. He talks in detail about some of the battles that he fought in Afghanistan against the Soviets.
  27:23 to the end of side B, recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura A?l ?Umra?n verses 176-188.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 31:23 ?????.. ??? ????? ?????? 31:02 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?????? ????? ???? ?? ??? ??????????? ?? ?????? ?? ???????, ????? ?????? ????? ??? ??????? ??????? ????????? ??? ??????? ???????? ?? ??????? ????????? ????? .???? ????? ???? ???? ?? ????? ???????? ???????? ?????? ???????? ???? ????. ????? ??? ??? ?????? ??????? ?? ???????. ???? ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??????. ????? ??? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?????????. ????? ?? ????? ???????? ???? ???? ?? ???????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 27:22 ????? ???????? ?? ????? ?????. ??????? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??? ?????? ??? ????????? ??????. ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ??????, ??? ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ????? ?????????, ?????? ?? ?????? ? ?????????, ??????? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????. ???? ?????? ??? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ????????? ?? ????????
  ?? 27:23 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ????? 176 ??? 188
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 495. Jihad in Palestine and Afghanistan, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 495)
  [Duplicate of Tape 494].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 496. A sermon on Jihad in Afghanistan and Palestine, 1989; 1 (Box 496)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 31:04 min. Side B 31:09 min. Side B is a duplicate of Tape 504, Side B. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Usa?mah ibn La?din. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker gives a sermon in which he talks in detail about some battles in which he fought with Mujahideen in Afghanistan against the Soviets. He speaks about a number of Mujahideen and mentions the names and where they came from. He speaks about Palestine and incites people to fight to retrieve Palestine. He incites people to go for a month to Afghanistan to get training to fight and he cites the opinion of ibn ?Uthaymi?n. The recording cuts off at the end of side A.
  0:00 to 26:10 Continuation of the same sermon from side A. The same speaker answers questions about Jihad in Palestine, boycott American goods, and getting the parents' consent to go for Jihad. He narrates stories about some of the Mujahideen in Afghanistan and speaks about conflicts among Afghanis. He answers questions about the role of physicians in Jihad and the US and other countries aid to equip Mujahideen with weapons.
  26:11 to the end of side B, Background noise.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 31:04 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:09 ?????. ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? 504. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ???? ????? ???? ???????? ?? ??? ?? ??????? ???? ????? ????????? ?? ?????????? ?? ???????? ?? ??? ??????? ???????? ???? ????? ????. ????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ??? ?????? ???????? ??????. ????? ????? ??? ?????? ???? ??? ??? ????????? ?????? ??? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ??????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 26:10 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????. ??? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ??????, ?????? ??????? ?????????, ??? ?? ??? ????????? ?? ?????????, ??? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????, ?????? ??? ???????, ??? ??????? ?? ??????, ?????????? ????????? ??? ????? ?????? ?????? ????????? ???????
  ?? 26:11 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 497. A seminar on the interpretation of the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 497)
  Comments: Side A 44:44 min. Side B 44:40 min.
  Side A: A recording of a seminar on the interpretation of the Qur?a?n in which a speaker defines interpretation and explains its rules. The speaker gives cites and interprets a number of verses from the Qur?a?n.
  Side B: The speaker explains the meaning of some words from the Qur?a?n and reviews different opinions and interpretations of a number of scholars from al-Sunnah wa-al-Jama??ah.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 44:44 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:40 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ??????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ??????? (???????) ??????? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ??? ?? ????? ??????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ???? ???????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???? ??? ????? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 498. A sermon on Jihad and the risks that surround the Islamic nation and the "land of the two holy sanctuaries", Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 498)
  [Duplicate of Tape 33].
  - Preservation masters, 1
  - Use copies, 1
- Tape 500. The foreign military presence in the Gulf, Arab and Middle East regions, Circa 1998-2000; 1 (Box 500)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 30:25 min. Side B 29:13 min. Speaker: Usa?mah ibn La?din and others. Place: Unknown.
  0:00 to 8:35 The tape starts with recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Baqarah verse 120. Then a speaker talks about the USA, UK, French, and Israeli military presence in Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Kuwait, Oman, Bahrain, Qatar, Turkey, Jordan, Palestine, Ba?b al-Mandab strait, Djibouti, Hormuz Strait, and Morocco. He lists numbers of soldiers, weapons, aircrafts, experts, armories, and naval fleets.
  8:36 to the end of side A, Another speaker who is Usa?mah ibn La?din gives a lecture on the US military presence in Saudi Arabia and the Gulf countries. He believes that this presence is an occupation and it shows the weakness of the Arab governments because they used foreign troops to liberate Kuwait from the Iraqi occupation. He accuses the governments of the Gulf countries of lying to their people about the foreign military presence in their countries.
  Side B: The last speaker on side A continues his lecture. He speaks about the occupation of Palestine and accuses the Arab governments of betraying and lying to their people. He strongly criticizes meetings of countries' leaders in Sharm al-Shaykh in Egypt to support Israel. He urges Jihad and fighting the Americans. He reviews a statement from the commander of the US military forces during the Gulf war in an interview with USA Today magazine. He mentions the name of Ayman al-Z?awa?hiri?.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 30:25 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:13 ?????. ???????: ????? ?? ???? ??????. ??????: ??? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 8:35 ???? ?????? ?????? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? 120 .??? ??? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ????????, ??????????, ?????????, ???????? ?? ???????? ,???, ??????, ????, ???????, ???, ?????, ?????? ,??????, ???? ??? ??????, ??????, ???? ????, ??????? ????? ???????, ??????, ???????, ????????, ??? ??????, ???????, ???????? ???????, ???????? ???????
  ?? 8:36 ??? ????? ????? ????? ????? ??? ???? ?????? ?? ?????? ???????? ?? ???????? ???? ?????? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ???????? ???? ???? ??? ??? ???????? ??????? ????? ??????? ????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???????? ???????. ???? ?????? ??? ?????? ?????? ??? ?????? ???? ?????? ??????? ??????? ?? ???????
  ????? ??????: ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ???? ???????. ????? ?? ???? ?????? ?????? ?????? ???????? ??????? ??????? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????. ????? ???? ???????? ????? ??? ?? ??? ????? ?? ??? ????? ???????. ???? ??? ?????? ????? ?????????. ???? ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ???? "?????? ?????". ???? ??? ???? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 501. A lecture on Jihad in Afghanistan, 1989; 1 (Box 501)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 32:00 min. Side B 30:58 min. Speaker: Usa?mah ibn La?din and others. Place: Saudi Arabia.